Akshay D

Software Engineer

💌 aksh.dk@gmail.com 📞 09066626690 in akshaykomarla 💡 Bengaluru, India 📙 Indian

Profile

I am a passionate and creative software engineer with expertise in **cloud and backend services**. I mostly work on Backend development with **Node.js and Golang (Go).**

4+ experience in developing proprietary enterprise software products and libraries. Team player with a can-do attitude, good time management skills.

I'm also an Arduino & Raspberry Pi hobbyist.

Skills

- Golang
- gRPC & Protocol Buffers
- Docker, Kubernetes & Helm
- Gitlab CI/CD & Github Actions
- $\bullet \ {\tt Javascript}$
- MySQL & PostgreSQL
- Firebase
- GCP & Digital Ocean
- Nodejs
- MongoDB & Firestore
- Prometheus & Grafana

Professional Experience

Falabella India, Software Engineer ☑

• My Orders: View, track, cancel orders, etc. Golang & gRPC framework.

- Credentials Cron Service: This service is responsible for keeping the **Auth0** machine to machine application tokens upto date in **kubernetes configmap / gcp secret manager**. **Golang**
- Credentials Package: This package is used to fetch the auth0 tokens from kubernetes configmap / gcp secret manager for communication between services. Also includes a fallback mechanism to fetch from **auth0** in case the tokens are not upto date.
- Eslint NPM Library: Created an NPM library to enforce coding standards and linting for javascript.

Terrace Tech Labs Pvt Ltd, Software Engineer ☑

04/2018 - 03/2019

03/2019 - present

- Anek: Learning Management System with personalised interactive 3D content for learners and Kanban layout for adaptive content creators. Node.js & React.js
- The Creeda: UK based platform for booking sports venues, grounds etc. Node.js & React.js
- Enovate Clothing: E-commerce clothing platform Node.js & React.js

Hexwhale Technologies Pvt Ltd, $Software\ Developer\ riangledown$

03/2016 - 03/2018

- Job Automation: Built A Job automation system for QA team to validate and reject. The system processes over 1000 jobs everyday. PHP and MySql.
- Veepee Dispatch App: A Dispatch Automation, maintenance and package tracking application. PHP and Android SDK.
- Veepee Customer App A mobile application job tracking application for customers. **Node.js** and **React Native**.
- Tavernut A mobile application which takes dine in requests to prepare food before the user reaches the restaurant. Node.js and React Native.

Education

South East Asian College Of Engineering & Technology,

09/2011 - 10/2015

B.E., Computer Science

aksh.dk@gmail.com 1 / 1